Toggle navigation

One stop shop for Train Simulator downloadable content, routes, scenarios, reskins, patches mods and user generated free, subscription and payware Train Sim addons.

Search for:  

    * [Train Sim World (TSW)](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/category/public/other-titles/train-sim-world-tsw/ "Train Sim World (TSW)")
            * [Diesel Multiple Unit (DMU)](https://alanthomsonsim.com/?product_cat=diesel-multiple-unit-dmu "Diesel Multiple Unit (DMU)")
            * [Electric Multiple Unit (EMU)](https://alanthomsonsim.com/?product_cat=electric-multiple-unit-emu "Electric Multiple Unit (EMU)")

Search for:  

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy Notice
=====================

**The policy:** This privacy policy notice is served by Alan Thomson Simulation Limited under the website; \[[www.alanthomsonsim.com](https://www.alanthomsonsim.com/ "Domain Title")\]. The purpose of this policy is to explain to you how we control, process, handle and protect your personal information through the business and while you browse or use this website. If you do not agree to the following policy you may wish to cease viewing / using this website, and or refrain from submitting your personal data to us.

**Policy key definitions:**

* “I”, “our”, “us”, or “we” refer to the business, \[Business name & other trading names\].
* “you”, “the user” refer to the person(s) using this website.
* GDPR means General Data Protection Act.
* PECR means Privacy & Electronic Communications Regulation.
* ICO means Information Commissioner’s Office.
* Cookies mean small files stored on a users computer or device.

**Key principles of GDPR:**

Our privacy policy embodies the following key priciples; (a) Lawfullness, fairness and transpatrency, (b) Purpose limitation, (c) Data minimisation, (d) Accurancy, (e) Storage limitation, (f) Integrity and confidence, (g) Accountability.

Processing of your personal data
--------------------------------

Under the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) we control and / or process any personal information about you electronically using the following lawful bases.

* We are exempt from registration in the ICO Data Protection Register because we are only processing personal data for the core business purposes.  
    **We process your information in the following ways:** To administer and process orders, downloads and notification emails linked to the administration of your account on our site. To prevent unlawful use or distribution of our products and for internal marketing purposes.  
    **Data retention period:** We will continue to process your information under this basis until you withdraw consent or it is determined your consent no longer exists.  
    **Sharing your information:** We share the following information with third parties;
* Order details where the product is not an Alan Thomson Simulation product and your details must be passed to a third party t process an order or where a promotion is run which includes products distributed by a third party. In this case we would share only the very minimum information with that third party for the purpose of processing your order or promotion product only.
* We share your name, email, product ordered and associated details of such product and address details with TS Controllers if you purchase one of their products so that they can process your order  
    
    * * *

If, as determined by us, the lawful basis upon which we process your personal information changes, we will notify you about the change and any new lawful basis to be used if required. We shall stop processing your personal information if the lawful basis used is no longer relevant.

Your individual rights
----------------------

Under the GDPR your rights are as follows. You can read more about [your rights in details here](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/ "your rights in details under the GDPR");

* the right to be informed;
* the right of access;
* the right to rectification;
* the right to erasure;
* the right to restrict processing;
* the right to data portability;
* the right to object; and
* the right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling.

You also have the right to complain to the ICO \[[www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/ "The ICO")\] if you feel there is a problem with the way we are handling your data.

We handle subject access requests in accordance with the GDPR.

Internet cookies
----------------

We use cookies on this website to provide you with a better user experience. We do this by placing a small text file on your device / computer hard drive to track how you use the website, to record or log whether you have seen particular messages that we display, to keep you logged into the website where applicable, to display relevant adverts or content, referred you to a third party website.

Some cookies are required to enjoy and use the full functionality of this website.

We use a cookie control system which allows you to accept the use of cookies, and control which cookies are saved to your device / computer. Some cookies will be saved for specific time periods, where others may last indefinitely. Your web browser should provide you with the controls to manage and delete cookies from your device, please see your web browser options.

Data security and protection
----------------------------

We ensure the security of any personal information we hold by using secure data storage technologies and precise procedures in how we store, access and manage that information. Our methods meet the GDPR compliance requirement.

### Fair & Transparent Privacy Explained

We have provided some further explanations about user privacy and the way we use this website to help promote a transparent and honest user privacy methodology.

### Sponsored links, affiliate tracking & commissions

Our website may contain adverts, sponsored and affiliate links on some pages. These are typically served through our advertising partners; Google Adsense, eBay Partner Network, Amazon Affiliates, or are self served through our own means. We only use trusted advertising partners who each have high standards of user privacy and security. However we do not control the actual adverts seen / displayed by our advertising partners. Our ad partners may collect data and use cookies for ad personalisation and measurement. Where ad preferences are requested as ‘non-personalised’ cookies may still be used for frequency capping, aggregated ad reporting and to combat fraud and abuse.

Clickable sponsored or affiliate links may be displayed as a website URL like this; www.example.co.uk/blog/welcome.php or as a titled text link like this: Example.

Clicking on any adverts, sponsored or affiliate links may track your actions by using a cookie saved to your device. You can read more about cookies on this website above. Your actions are usually recorded as a referral from our website by this cookie. In most cases we earn a very small commission from the advertiser or advertising partner, at no cost to you, whether you make a purchase on their website or not.

We use advertising partners in these ways to help generate an income from the website, which allows us to continue our work and provide you with the best overall experience and valued information.

If you have any concerns about this we suggest you do not click on any adverts, sponsored or affiliate links found throughout the website.

### Email marketing messages & subscription

Under the GDPR we use the consent lawful basis for anyone subscribing to our newsletter or marketing mailing list. We only collect certain data about you, as detailed in the “Processing of your personal date” above. Any email marketing messages we send are done so through an EMS, email marketing service provider. An EMS is a third party service provider of software / applications that allows marketers to send out email marketing campaigns to a list of users.

Email marketing messages that we send may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of data such as; times, dates, I.P addresses, opens, clicks, forwards, geographic and demographic data. Such data, within its limitations will show the activity each subscriber made for that email campaign.

Any email marketing messages we send are in accordance with the GDPR and the PECR. We provide you with an easy method to withdraw your consent (unsubscribe) or manage your preferences / the information we hold about you at any time. See any marketing messages for instructions on how to unsubscribe or manage your preferences, you can also [unsubscribe from all MailChimp lists](http://www.jamieking.co.uk/blog/cyber-security/my-cyber/unsubscribe-from-all-global-mailchimp-lists.php "Unsubscribe from all MailChimp lists"), by following this link, otherwise contact the EMS provider.

#### Resources & further information

Number of items in basket: 0

* Your basket is empty.
* Total: £0.00

### Product categories

Select a category ATS Launcher – Routes ATS Launcher – Scenarios ATS Launcher – Rolling Merchandise    Mugs Train Simulator    Rolling Stock       Diesel Locomotive       Diesel Multiple Unit (DMU)       Electric Locomotive       Electric Multiple Unit (EMU)       On Track Plant       Steam       Wagon    Routes    Scenarios    Scenery

### Alan thomson simulation on youtube

[

](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCz_EV9jfJqRS1pI7Z8vYdGg)

### ALAN THOMSON SIMULATION ON TWITCH

[

](https://www.twitch.tv/alanthomsonsim)

### Train Simulator News Index

### Latest News

[

](https://alanthomsonsim.com/west-coast-mainline-midlands-northwest-phase-4-stoke-loop-coming-soon/ "West Coast Mainline Midlands & Northwest – Phase 4 – STOKE LOOP – AVAILABLE NOW!")

26th December 2021 Off

[West Coast Mainline Midlands & Northwest – Phase 4 – STOKE LOOP – AVAILABLE NOW!](https://alanthomsonsim.com/west-coast-mainline-midlands-northwest-phase-4-stoke-loop-coming-soon/)
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

By [Alan Thomson Simulation](https://alanthomsonsim.com/author/admin/)

Alan Thomsom Sim presents the latest addition to the West Coast Mainline Midlands & Northwest: Phase 4 - Stoke Loop This brand new route extends the existing network adding the historic Potteries area to Train Simulator 2022. The route features...

16th November 2020 Off

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

By [Gareth Davies](https://alanthomsonsim.com/author/daviesg77/)

Dovetail has released a second major patch for the WCML South. DTG seems to be committed to the continued update...

1st July 2020 Off

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

By [Alan Thomson Simulation](https://alanthomsonsim.com/author/admin/)

Courtesy of MKS, we are proud to host their Class 460 'Airlines' reskin pack. This pack contains three reskins :...

### Product Updates

14th March 2024 Off

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

By [Alan Thomson Simulation](https://alanthomsonsim.com/author/admin/)

The following Just Trains products have been updated. The updated installers can be found in your account on their order...

25th January 2024 Off

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

By [Alan Thomson Simulation](https://alanthomsonsim.com/author/admin/)

Latest Update: 2024/01/24 The below log shows all updates for...

16th April 2023 Off

----------------------------------------------------

By [Alan Thomson Simulation](https://alanthomsonsim.com/author/admin/)

You can view product changelogs here

### Just trains available here

[

](https://alanthomsonsim.com/?yith_shop_vendor=just-trains)

### Random Download

*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1s51-1127-plymouth-to-glasgow-central/ "1S51 1127 Plymouth to Glasgow Central")[1S51 1127 Plymouth to Glasgow Central](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1s51-1127-plymouth-to-glasgow-central/ "1S51 1127 Plymouth to Glasgow Central")

### Top 10 Most Popular

*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/intercity-225-lner-vtec-pack/ "InterCity 225 LNER/VTEC Pack")[InterCity 225 LNER/VTEC Pack](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/intercity-225-lner-vtec-pack/ "InterCity 225 LNER/VTEC Pack")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/berks-and-hants-to-bristol-and-penzance-v2/ "Berks and Hants to Bristol and Penzance V4.1")[Berks and Hants to Bristol and Penzance V4.1](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/berks-and-hants-to-bristol-and-penzance-v2/ "Berks and Hants to Bristol and Penzance V4.1")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/vtec-lner-hst-pack/ "VTEC & LNER HST Pack")[VTEC & LNER HST Pack](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/vtec-lner-hst-pack/ "VTEC & LNER HST Pack")
*  [ [V1.4]")
    
     [V1.4]")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ybzg-pdl-london-waterloo-to-portsmouth-harbour-updated-v1-1/ "[YBZG] PDL (Updated) [V1.4]")[\[YBZG\] PDL (Updated) \[V1.4\]](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ybzg-pdl-london-waterloo-to-portsmouth-harbour-updated-v1-1/ "[YBZG] PDL (Updated) [V1.4]")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/class-80x-extra-equipments-patch/ "Class 80x extra equipments patch 1.5.4")[Class 80x extra equipments patch 1.5.4](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/class-80x-extra-equipments-patch/ "Class 80x extra equipments patch 1.5.4")
*  [")
    
    ")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/west-coast-mainline-midlands-and-northwest-aka-missing-link/ "West Coast Mainline Midlands and Northwest (aka - 'Missing Link')")[West Coast Mainline Midlands and Northwest (aka – ‘Missing Link’)](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/west-coast-mainline-midlands-and-northwest-aka-missing-link/ "West Coast Mainline Midlands and Northwest (aka - 'Missing Link')")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/class-66-led-headlights/ "Class 66 LED Headlights")[Class 66 LED Headlights](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/class-66-led-headlights/ "Class 66 LED Headlights")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ats-launcher/ "ATS Launcher")[ATS Launcher](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ats-launcher/ "ATS Launcher")
*  [")
    
    ")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ap-track-patch-and-replacement-signal-lens-textures-for-just-trains/ "AP Track Patch and Replacement Signal Lens Textures for Just Trains (V15.02)")[AP Track Patch and Replacement Signal Lens Textures for Just Trains (V15.02)](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ap-track-patch-and-replacement-signal-lens-textures-for-just-trains/ "AP Track Patch and Replacement Signal Lens Textures for Just Trains (V15.02)")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ats-class-700-patch/ "ATS Class 700/717 Patch")[ATS Class 700/717 Patch](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/ats-class-700-patch/ "ATS Class 700/717 Patch")

### Most Recent Additions

*  [ 5Q48 19:42 Hornsey E.M.U.D.-Norwich C.PT.&R.S.M.D.")
    
     5Q48 19:42 Hornsey E.M.U.D.-Norwich C.PT.&R.S.M.D.")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/jr-5q48-1942-hornsey-e-m-u-d-norwich-c-pt-r-s-m-d/ "(JR) 5Q48 19:42 Hornsey E.M.U.D.-Norwich C.PT.&R.S.M.D.")[(JR) 5Q48 19:42 Hornsey E.M.U.D.-Norwich C.PT.&R.S.M.D.](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/jr-5q48-1942-hornsey-e-m-u-d-norwich-c-pt-r-s-m-d/ "(JR) 5Q48 19:42 Hornsey E.M.U.D.-Norwich C.PT.&R.S.M.D.")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/5q87-1439-ely-to-liverpool-st/ "5Q87 1439 Ely to Liverpool St")[5Q87 1439 Ely to Liverpool St](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/5q87-1439-ely-to-liverpool-st/ "5Q87 1439 Ely to Liverpool St")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/5q84-1330-stansted-airport-to-ely/ "5Q84 1330 Stansted Airport to Ely")[5Q84 1330 Stansted Airport to Ely](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/5q84-1330-stansted-airport-to-ely/ "5Q84 1330 Stansted Airport to Ely")
*  [ – 1S53 06:57 Coventry – Edinburgh [Part 1]")
    
     – 1S53 06:57 Coventry – Edinburgh [Part 1]")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/the-big-freeze-1991-1s53-0657-coventry-edinburgh-part-1/ "The Big Freeze (1991) – 1S53 06:57 Coventry – Edinburgh [Part 1]")[The Big Freeze (1991) – 1S53 06:57 Coventry – Edinburgh \[Part 1\]](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/the-big-freeze-1991-1s53-0657-coventry-edinburgh-part-1/ "The Big Freeze (1991) – 1S53 06:57 Coventry – Edinburgh [Part 1]")
*  [ – 5N30 10:10 Oxenholme - Preston [Part 2]")
    
     – 5N30 10:10 Oxenholme - Preston [Part 2]")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/the-big-freeze-1991-5n30-1010-oxenholme-preston-part-2/ "The Big Freeze (1991) – 5N30 10:10 Oxenholme - Preston [Part 2]")[The Big Freeze (1991) – 5N30 10:10 Oxenholme – Preston \[Part 2\]](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/the-big-freeze-1991-5n30-1010-oxenholme-preston-part-2/ "The Big Freeze (1991) – 5N30 10:10 Oxenholme - Preston [Part 2]")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/mjt-5q06-0821-merchant-park-sidings-oxley-car-m-d/ "[mjt] 5Q06 08:21 Merchant Park Sidings - Oxley Car. M.D.")[\[mjt\] 5Q06 08:21 Merchant Park Sidings – Oxley Car. M.D.](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/mjt-5q06-0821-merchant-park-sidings-oxley-car-m-d/ "[mjt] 5Q06 08:21 Merchant Park Sidings - Oxley Car. M.D.")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/2j90-1520-westbury-to-exeter-st-davids/ "2J90 1520 Westbury to Exeter St Davids")[2J90 1520 Westbury to Exeter St Davids](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/2j90-1520-westbury-to-exeter-st-davids/ "2J90 1520 Westbury to Exeter St Davids")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/mjt-1z90-0815-london-kings-cross-newcastle/ "[mjt] 1Z90 08:15 London Kings Cross - Newcastle")[\[mjt\] 1Z90 08:15 London Kings Cross – Newcastle](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/mjt-1z90-0815-london-kings-cross-newcastle/ "[mjt] 1Z90 08:15 London Kings Cross - Newcastle")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1p29-1100-norwich-to-liverpool-st/ "1P29 1100 Norwich to Liverpool St")[1P29 1100 Norwich to Liverpool St](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1p29-1100-norwich-to-liverpool-st/ "1P29 1100 Norwich to Liverpool St")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/2f05-braintree-witham-shuttle/ "2F05 Braintree - Witham Shuttle")[2F05 Braintree – Witham Shuttle](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/2f05-braintree-witham-shuttle/ "2F05 Braintree - Witham Shuttle")
*  [")
    
    ")](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1m29-1950-norwich-willesden-rmt-1998/ "1M29 19:50 Norwich - Willesden RMT (1998)")[1M29 19:50 Norwich – Willesden RMT (1998)](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1m29-1950-norwich-willesden-rmt-1998/ "1M29 19:50 Norwich - Willesden RMT (1998)")
*  [
    
    ](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1p34-1400-liverpool-st-to-norwich/ "1P34 1400 Liverpool St to Norwich")[1P34 1400 Liverpool St to Norwich](https://alanthomsonsim.com/downloads/1p34-1400-liverpool-st-to-norwich/ "1P34 1400 Liverpool St to Norwich")

### (c) Alan Thomson Simulation Ltd 2022

Copyright 2022 Alanthomsonsim.com – all rights reserved.

Alan Thomson Simulation limited – Registered in England & Wales 11784130

All prices displayed are inclusive of UK VAT @ 20% : UK VAT Number – 365 5500 95

### Useful Links

_All product names, trademarks and registered trademarks are property of their respective owners. All company, product and service names used in this website are for identification purposes only. Use of these names,trademarks and brands does not imply endorsement._

Proudly powered by [WordPress](https://wordpress.org/) | Theme: [Envo Magazine](https://envothemes.com/)

##### Cookie settings

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept and close Settings Reject [Read More](https://alanthomsonsim.com/?page_id=3)  

Privacy & Cookies Policy

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.

Non-necessary

 Non-necessary

Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.

SAVE & ACCEPT

Insert/edit link
================

Close

Enter the destination URL

URL 

Link Text 

 Open link in a new tab

Or link to existing content

Search 

_No search term specified. Showing recent items._ _Search or use up and down arrow keys to select an item._

Cancel
